ltlprints.com 2019-04-26

# Privacy Policy - Larger Than Life Prints

We value your privacy! We will never sell, lease or give or otherwise distribute your personal information. Period! Any information you give to LTLprints.com will be handled with the utmost care. We will not use your information in ways to which you have not consented. A more detailed explanation about how we safeguard your personal information is described below. If you have any questions at all about our privacy policy, please email us [privacy@LTLprints.com](mailto:privacy@LTLprints.com).

**Resale or disclosure of information to third parties  
** LTLprints.com does not rent, trade, loan, sell or lease any personal information collected at our site, including contact forms, download requests or email lists.

**Browser information collected on the web site  
** LTlprints.com analyzes the web site logs to improve the value of the materials and services offered on the web site.

#### Privacy Policy

**Resale or disclosure of information to third parties  
** When you register and use LTLprints.com, you provide information to us. In the following three sections, we explain what information is collected, how it is used, and the choices that you have with your information.

**Information Collected by LTLprints.com.  
** Depending on how you interact with LTLprints.com, you provide us with information, which may include: (a) your name, email address, phone number, age (to comply with legal requirements) and other registration information; (b) demographic, psychometric and other survey information about your interests and preferences; (c) payment information for purchases; (d) your interaction with LTLprints.com features and advertisements; (e) transaction-related information, such as, when you make purchases, respond to any offers, or download software from us; and (f) information you provide us when you contact us for help. We also collect other non-personally identifiable data, which may include your IP address and what browser you are using so that we can improve LTLprints.com's services to you.

**Use of Information  
** We will use your user ID or user name so that we can personalize your experience. We will use your email address to contact you from time to time regarding your purchases and LTLprints.com services. We may use your information (a) to deliver the LTLprints.com services and features desired by you, including any purchase that you make, (b) to improve our services to you, (c) to personalize content and offers that may be of interest to you, (d) to respond to your inquiries, and (e) to fulfill your request for products or services.  
We may use the non-personally identifiable information, like your IP address, to statistically analyze site usage and to customize our site's content, layout and services. The resulting information will allow us to improve our services and better understand and serve our users.  
We do not sell customer lists. We will not share any information that identifies you personally with any third party for marketing purposes. We will only share your information with third parties to provide services and products that you have requested or where we have your consent. We will disclose your personally identifiable information if we reasonably believe we are required to do so by law, regulation or other government authority or to protect our rights and property or the rights and property of the public.  
We may also cooperate with law enforcement agencies in any official investigation and we may disclose your personally identifiable information to the relevant agency in doing so. We may use subcontractors or agents in order to help provide our services to you. Any subcontractor that we use must agree to keep your information confidential and subject to the terms of this privacy policy. 

**How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information  
** You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by signing into your account with LTLprints under[ www.LTLprints.com/login](https://beta.rifluxyss.com/t5/ltlprints/signup.php) and subsequently clicking on ['My Account'](https://beta.rifluxyss.com/t5/ltlprints/signup.php). We use this procedure to better safeguard your information.  
You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows the error or by maintaining your account information under [www.LTLprints.com/login](https://beta.rifluxyss.com/t5/ltlprints/signup.php) and subsequently clicking on ['My Account'.](https://beta.rifluxyss.com/t5/ltlprints/signup.php)  
To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

**Minors  
** Children under the age of thirteen (13) are not eligible to use our service and must not submit any personal information to us.  
To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

**Use of Cookies  
** Cookies are a standard Internet technology, and many major web sites use them to provide useful features for their members. Cookies allow us to store and retrieve login information on a user's system. They provide us with data that we can use to improve the quality of our service and make it easier to use. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. If you'd prefer, you can set yours to refuse cookies. However, you may not be able to take full advantage of LTLprints.com if you do so.  

**Acquisition  
** We reserve the right to transfer your personal information in the event of a transfer of ownership of LTLprints.com LLC, such as acquisition by or merger with another company. If an acquiring company should plan to materially change this privacy policy, we will notify you beforehand.

**Security  
** The security of your personal information depends on your protection of your account password. Please do not disclose your account password to unauthorized people. We use industry standard technology designed to help keep your personal information safe. If you have any other questions about the security of our website, please contact us at [privacy@LTLprints.com](mailto:privacy@LTLprints.com).

**Changes in Privacy Policy  
** From time to time we may update this Privacy Policy and will post a notice of any significant changes on our website. You should visit this page periodically to review any such changes to the privacy policy. Your continued use of this website or our service and/or continued provision of personally identifiable information to us will be subject to the terms of the then-current Privacy Policy.

**Canceling Your Account  
** You always have the option to cancel your account with us at any time. Simply send an email [privacy@LTLprints.com](mailto:privacy@LTLprints.com) to cancel your account.

**How to Contact Us  
** If you have any questions or concerns about LTLprints.com's Privacy Policy or its implementation, you may contact us at this email address: [privacy@LTLprints.com](mailto:privacy@LTLprints.com)  

**Changes  
** LTLprints.com may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. Therefore, you should review this Policy periodically. If there are significant changes to LTLprints.com's information practices, you will be provided with appropriate online notice. You may be provided other privacy-related information in connection with your use of offerings from LTLprints.com, as well as for special features and services not described in this Policy that may be introduced in the future. Updated 11-23-2008
